Well, I don't know
who I'll be traveling with yet.
They wouldn't tell me anything.
I've been wondering who it might be.
The mystery makes this trip
that much more thrilling.
It's as if something
that only happens in a movie
is happening to me.
Anyway, I'm really
very nervous and excited.
Wow!
Hold on to this. It's hot.
The reason every moment
of our journey has been beautiful…
is that you
were a part of the scenery.
But there's a scene in a movie I like
where the lead characters
attend the opera.
Do you know the film Pretty Woman
starring Julia Roberts?
Next time,
let's go see that opera you memorized.
It's good.
It's a mix. It's a mix.
Kanpai.
-Kanpai.
Oh, it went there.
Beautiful.
So much that I can't look away.
I…
really like you, Cha Mu-hee.
Okay.
Thank you.
Me too.
We did it.
Mm.
That was a first cut.
What do you think? Romantic, isn't it?
Just in case you're worried,
audiences are used to
fake on-screen romance.
No one really expects
any of it to be real.
Unless you start dating
and end up in a scandal.
You two aren't a couple, right?
Also, to be clear,
we think the show's in really great shape.
But if you want us
to change some things, we can.
We don't want anyone's feelings
to be hurt.
There's no point in us
taking advantage of real feelings.
I'm fine with it. I've got no complaints.
Wh… what? When did you learn English?
Just now.
Wow, Hiro!
Look at that! Did you hear that?
Well, the truth
is that when I met you for the first time,
I immediately liked you.
And then when
I found out that you were
Jin-suk's brother, I was, uh…
I was embarrassed and felt awkward.
You must have known
that I had feelings for you.
I had to be very careful around you too.
I didn't want you to know either.
Does that mean…
Ho-jin, you… were into me?
I was.
I never had imagined this would be
something I'd share with you.
But since we're comfortable talking,
the zombie film
that felt like it would never end,
it's, uh… it's finally over for good.
The zombie film?
It'll be at least another two hours.
I'll need that long to explain everything
without any misunderstandings.
I should begin with what happened
on that island.
Let's do it. So the photo taken of you
on the island,
Mu-hee was with you then?
Yeah, that's right.
That was actually the day
that she and I met for the first time.
You said you wanted revenge,
so I thought you were going
to ask to change things.
Thanks for saying it's fine.
Don't bother thanking me.
That's not my revenge.
It's a different thing.
Tell me, what is it?
I'm going to "review" everything.
-What?
-Mm.
No, not that.
I'm going to reveal everything.
Okay, about what?
I'm going to spill the beans
and just tell him
that you never had any interest in me.
Tell who?
Are you playing dumb?
That guy who speaks so many languages.
I will tell him everything.
You mean Ho-jin?
Mm.
He knows.
He already knows.
-He knows?
-I told him everything.
And I even… asked him to help
make things work with you.
So wait,
you said everything to the guy you like?
Are you
simple-minded?
No.
I'm not dumb or anything.
I'm just crazy.
Just imagine that I'm like Do Ra-mi.
Totally unpredictable.
I just wanted to tease you,
but you're no fun.
Hiro,
you're amazing.
On screen,
you're even more handsome, you know?
I know.
I kept thinking while we were filming,
how I'd like a relationship
with a man like you.
All I'd have to do would be to stand there
and enjoy amazing and beautiful views.
No anxieties. No problems.
Just living happily ever after
with you until the very end.
Yes. That's why Do Ra-mi, uh…
No, that's why
I acted the way I did with you.
It's all my fault.
I wanted you to like me.
I strung you along.
So I'm really sorry.
And thank you.
You were…
the real-life version
of the prince I was dreaming of.
A beautiful escape from reality.
You'll be okay…
Did you get that?
I don't know.
-I don't think so.
-Oh, you understood. You did.
You're kind of a genius.
How did you learn English so fast?
You're really great.
When I met you
by the clock tower in Italy,
and when you asked me if I liked you,
I've wondered what might have been
if I'd just been honest and said yes.
I regretted not having done so.
-I'm so bitter about that.
-So babe, I promise
Forever, I'll never leave…
Hmm. I'm really sorry.
I wish I could understand Japanese.
You're…
pretty dumb.
What?
So stay close…
My mom's picking me up here.
I'm going to go that way.
Okay. I'm going to catch a taxi.
Goodbye, then.
Take care.
So babe, I promise
I won't ever leave
When you're down and falling
Know that I'll be there…
Forever, I'll never leave…
CAN THIS LOVE BE TRANSLATED?
I heard you're looking
to donate some antique books
which belonged to your dear friend.
As you know,
the university's library
would be an ideal place.
I've been talking it over
with your friend.
I wasn't expecting
that you'd want to get involved, Mr. Kim.
-That's great.
-Well, you see--
Oh, wait.
That's not the reason we're here.
I wanted to ask you
certain questions about someone.
Your youngest brother?
Sure.
What would you like to know about him?
He passed away a long time ago.
Did he leave behind a young daughter?
And that's the child you adopted.
Is that right?
And her name is…
It's, uh, Cha Mu-hee.
Yes, her name's Mu-hee.
Well, something does seem
a little bit strange.
My friend over here said
your little brother died
when he was young.
-From a serious illness.
-Yes, you said from a serious illness.
But Cha Mu-hee told me
her parents died in an accident.
Huh.
Well, Mr. Kim, um, how do you know her?
Are you friends with Mu-hee?
Yes, yes.
We've seen each other many times.
We've shared a meal together
and even attended
a musical event with each other.
That's right. We were both there.
Mu-hee was with the grandson
whose mother owns the antiques you want.
-They make a cute couple.
-That's enough.
They're very important to us.
His grandson is like the son I never had.
I have concerns,
and I hope you don't take any offense.
You say you're like a father to him.
Please tell him this. "Stop seeing her."
"Stop seeing her"?
I know she's adopted, but she's now
like a daughter to you, right?
We adopted her
because she's part of the family.
But we didn't want to.
That child was impossible.
We adopted her only because we had to.
I just arrived.
I'm at the station near my house,
but it's already so late.
It's not that late.
There aren't too many people around.
It's past midnight.
Aren't you booked for something
early in the morning?
Are you very tired?
Hmm. Well, you were working all day
and started early.
You're tired.
But, uh, didn't you sleep on the train?
Forget it.
Taking a nap on the train isn't real rest.
If you're really too tired,
then it's okay.
I slept enough on the train,
and I've got energy, so here I am.
Thanks for meeting me.
You knew I was here? Did you see me?
You sounded pretty disappointed,
so I figured you were here.
It's because you came back late.
I came to see you
so we'd have time together. Even a little.
Let's go.
Why is your hand so cold?
Were you waiting for a while?
But you were going to leave?
Yes. Um, I hadn't told you I was here,
so I was gonna go.
Cha Mu-hee. Hmm.
Please pay attention.
I want you to hear this.
Even if I never sleep on the train,
I always want you to come see me.
That's how much I like you.
Though if I don't sleep for four days,
I might die.
Where do you wanna go?
There's a lookout I wanna take you to.
The birds are flying
I heard it in the sky
Something they want to imply…
I love it here.
Wow.
The view's great, isn't it?
Too bad we can't see the stars better.
Do you wanna see them?
I know of a great place to see the stars.
-It's in Seoul?
-Yeah.
It's called Dark Sky International.
Dark Sky International?
Something like that exists?
Its mission is to protect the night sky
from any sort of light pollution.
This was the first Asian country
to be officially preserved
as a dark-sky zone,
so we can see the stars.
Oh!
Is that like the Michelin Guide
giving stars to restaurants?
Yes, yes.
It's a hotspot for the stars.
You can even see the Milky Way from there.
The Milky Way?
I've heard about it,
but I've never had a chance to see it.
-Let's go see it?
-Of course.
We saw the Northern Lights,
and now we'll see the Milky Way.
Oh, I just hope the weather's good.
I'll collect four-leaf clovers.
Yes. Go and do your best.
Ho-jin, I've been thinking.
You're taller than me.
It makes you closer to the sky.
So you'll be able
to see the stars better than I will.
You sure?
Let's check.
How is it?
Ah, cheers, my fears…
-Hey!
-You okay?
-Can you see them better?
-That was fun.
I see them better.
Oh!
So many words are shining
Like the big stars
And I pick one from the sky
Stuck in my throat
Round and round
I wanna speak out
But no one's there
Echoes of my voice
Answer alone
Tell me the truth
What don't I see?
Stuck in my thoughts
I walk till I fade
I feel the love in the morning sun
But why am I blue all again?
Round and round, my life just goes on…
-Everyone has their glasses?
-Absolutely.
To Ji-sun for breaking off her engagement.
Yes.
Cheers!
There's no need to be embarrassed.
Breaking off an engagement is badass!
I'm a badass?
Even if you break off an engagement
ten times, you're still our hero.
-Of course.
-Don't get divorced like her.
Nothing's wrong with that.
Do you want me to introduce you to a guy?
How about a guy
who owns a building in Seoul?
If you like tall and good-looking guys,
it's a match.
Wanna meet him?
-Ji-sun doesn't need our help.
-Yup.
She's surrounded by so many hot guys.
Ji-sun, you should date a celebrity.
That'd be great, right?
-A good-looking older one.
-Yes.
It's okay. There's this one guy I met,
and I already like him.
Really?
Really! He's tall, so handsome,
and much younger than me.
Did I tell you that? He's younger?
-You're a cougar!
-You got yourself a younger man!
Let's go! Do you have pictures of him?
-Let's see.
-I wanna see this young, hot guy.
-You wanna see him? Okay.
-Show us. Let's see him.
Let me show you, then.
-She's gonna show us.
-Let's see him!
Oh?
Kim Yong-u?
But I'm looking at him on the phone.
How's he standing there?
Hello, ladies.
I'm the new guy she's dating.
The younger, handsome boyfriend.
Oh.
-He's so good-looking.
-Well, hello there.
Hot.
-Hey.
-How'd you know I'd be here?
You told me you're meeting
your friends around there.
I did a loop around the whole area.
So then, why did you come over here?
I came to tell you something very urgent,
but it turns out I have great timing.
It was nothing.
I said Jin-suk and I are done.
My friends were trying to be positive,
and I may have shown off.
You know.
Yes, showing off.
It's good for me, hmm,
as the one who gets shown off.
Thanks so much.
What is it? What's your urgent thing?
Ji-sun…
will you
marry me?
What?
Let's get married.
This is amazing! Come on!
Say yes already!
The answer's yes!
-Will you accept his proposal?
-Hey!
-Stop it!
-Marry him!
Marry him!
-She's gonna say yes!
-They're running away!
Go and get married, you love birds!
-Wow!
-Love birds!
It's what I came up with.
I know it's sudden.
I don't want us to break up.
Did I say I was breaking up with you?
I'm getting transferred.
I'm moving to the UK.
I'll be working with an athlete.
I want this opportunity,
so I'm not turning it down,
but I don't wanna lose you.
Do you think without you around,
I'm going to cheat or something?
You wouldn't do that.
I can't ask you to follow me,
so at least marry me.
I won't.
We don't need to get married.
That would be a little rash.
Let's just go together.
Once I'm done with work on the show,
I had already planned
on taking a long break,
at least for a year-long sabbatical
to study abroad.
I was going to do this for myself,
even after I ended the engagement.
I thought about studying overseas.
I could switch my plans to somewhere else.
But you never shared any of this.
Well, I have been wondering
if I should leave or not.
If it would be better to stay.
I wondered if I was overthinking it.
Hmm.
I'm so grateful you thought about me.
Someone told me
you're good at British accents.
I was shocked.
I'm bilingual.
I speak Scottish, my friend,
and I speak Cockney faintly.
How about the Queen's accent?
I think you could pick that one up.
Pleasant day!
Your Royal Highness.
I'm sleeping without having to take
any medications, and Do Ra-mi is gone now.
But why has she stopped coming to see me?
I thought about it a lot.
Is it because
I finally shared a big secret
I've been keeping to myself
with someone I really trust?
Could that be the reason why she's gone?
What kind of secret?
Well, it's just a childhood incident.
Is Do Ra-mi from your childhood?
Could it all be related?
She couldn't have existed
when I was a kid.
Or could she represent
someone else from your childhood?
She only came to see you
after the film was made.
Could the person you're seeing
be someone who is like Do Ra-mi?
I'm pretty sure it was Do Ra-mi,
but the doctor said it might not be.
You've met her,
and she said her name's Do Ra-mi, right?
She said it all came
from your own mind, Mu-hee.
Maybe she called herself that
because you believed it.
She looked like me,
so I thought she was me.
She was also very scary
and always criticized me.
Are you still with the doctor?
No.
I'm buying Yong-u's present.
He's like a little brother to me,
and he's leaving.
-Are you at home right now?
-I am.
A guest is supposed to come over soon.
A guest?
Your friend, the writer?
Ah.
Not Young-hwan.
I'll say more later when we're together.
Later? Not now?
All right, in the evening.
You could have emerged for many reasons,
but it may have to do with
that dark and sad past of hers.
A deep kind of pain.
Would you have this in a larger size?
-Yes, we do. I'll go get it.
-Thank you so much.
You're buying a gift?
Ah.
I heard your grandfather
had a great collection,
but seeing it, it's even more impressive.
It's much more than what I was expecting.
Is there some information
you have to tell me in person?
Ah.
I had hoped to convince you
to make a donation first.
It's for my foundation.
These belong to my mother,
and I can't just donate them.
Ah.
That's what I thought.
I guess Mu-hee has implied
that we had mistreated her.
Well, you must have mistreated her
when she was little
to jump to that conclusion.
We were quite strict with her.
She's a cunning girl
who told us a lot of lies.
She always said whatever suited her.
Sounds like she was clever
and had to adapt in order to survive.
She couldn't be honest with you
because she was living in a house of lies.
Mm.
As a child,
you weren't as greedy as you are now.
Suddenly, you're buying things
you can't afford,
now that you're somewhat famous.
I'm not just somewhat famous.
I've earned a lot of money.
I can afford things. All of it.
You remind me so much of her.
Of whom?
As we speak,
your uncle is meeting with Ho-jin
to ask for a contribution.
You will come up in their conversation.
Your boyfriend's family
could be a great help to us.
Don't buy items that you can't afford.
Just 'cause it looks like
things have been going well for you.
Hold on.
Mu-hee's mother isn't part of our family.
My brother and that woman never married.
She tried her best to use their kid
to stop him from leaving her,
but when that plan
didn't work out how she wanted,
she made a terrible choice
to try and ruin everything.
That's the kind of genes Mu-hee carries.
It's a shameful part of our history
that we need to keep hidden.
I understand
that you and Mu-hee are close.
I wanted to meet with you
to make you aware of what I know.
You didn't have to come and say all this
because I've already been warned.
Mu-hee has already said everything
I need to know.
That girl told you everything?
My boyfriend already knows.
I told him everything.
You already told him?
Yeah, I did.
I explained it all.
You told him everything?
Hmm.
I knew it.
You do remember everything
that happened to them.
Back then, on your birthday.
I said I didn't… that I didn't know
because I was so terrified.
I thought you would kick me out if I did.
Yes, I know everything.
Mu-hee,
happy birthday.
have a piece of cake too.
We can all finally be happy together.
She put poison
in her daughter's birthday cake.
She wanted them all to die.
Maybe Mu-hee refused and tried to run.
She fell off the balcony of the condo.
She kept saying
she remembered nothing of that day.
I thought it'd be the best for her.
No, you turned your back on her.
She's been alone
and burdened with these awful memories
since she was little. Her whole life.
I felt sorry for her,
but she's the daughter of a killer
who ruined our life.
This is a photo of her mother
that I've held on to.
I only kept it to show Mu-hee
if she ever asked to know more.
Do you see why being with Mu-hee
is a terrible reminder?
None of it was my fault.
Why did you hate me?
You've hated me for so long.
We were afraid.
You terrified us.
So you remember everything.
So, do you remember your mother too?
Well, then.
You wouldn't forget your mother.
You look at that face every day.
It's there in the mirror.
You've never forgotten your mother,
have you?
My mom…
looked like me, so I thought she was me.
She was also very scary
and always criticized me.
That face could only be Do Ra-mi's.
It was my mother.
Do Ra-mi
was my mom.
Finally, you recognize my face.
Here.
We can all be happy together.
Eat some cake.
No, please.
The little bird died
after eating just a few crumbs,
and Dad died too.
Do you want to be alone?
Why?
There's no one left.
No one in this world
will love you, Mu-hee.
You'll never find love or happiness.
I won't eat any.
Mommy?
I couldn't
completely run away
from my mother that day.
The words she said about me
have kept playing
in my head over and over again.
They've followed me everywhere.
So once again, with all of my strength,
and for the very last time,
I have to force you to go away.
One more time to finally make sure,
I will leave you alone
and go away forever.
Mu-hee,
I love you.
Cha Mu-hee? Are you awake?
Oh, you have no idea
how worried I was about you.
You've been here for three days.
Oh, come on. I'm fine.
The doctors told me
they didn't find anything wrong.
Oh, I let Ho-jin know you're good.
He's on his way and should be here soon.
Thank you.
Hey.
Oh no. I haven't bathed or washed my hair.
It looks like she's back. Thank goodness.
If you hadn't, Ho-jin would have died.
He wanted to stay here,
but with reporters outside
and staff coming in and out,
he stayed home, but didn't sleep or eat.
Hiro!
Ms. Cha Mu-hee is awake.
Really? Is she okay?
I spoke to Mr. Kim Yong-u on the phone,
and he said she's well.
I knew it.
There's no way
a zombie would die so easily.
Oh no. I'm exhausted.
Hey, are you okay?
You've spent three days
going at it with that punching bag.
I was worried you might collapse too.
I won't collapse from this!
Take this off me.
I don't have the strength to do it myself.
Your hands are trembling.
-I'm fine.
-You shouldn't overexert yourself.
This is all that zombie's fault.
When I see her,
I'm going to get my revenge.
Why are you always going on about revenge?
My mother and I look so much alike.
She's not the same person as you,
and you'll never be like her. Not one bit.
I know.
Mu-hee.
I need to tell you
one thing you don't know.
That day,
on your birthday, all those years ago,
a neighbor reported your fall.
So when the police entered your home,
they found both of your parents,
and they saved them.
Um…
Your parents are alive.
The father you thought had died
is healthy and lives in another country.
You've known him as the youngest uncle.
He survived.
Why would no one tell me?
Even as a kid,
I never spent much time with Dad.
That's why I don't remember his face.
After what happened,
your father's side of the family
lost contact with your mother.
I know she's still alive.
Why would they lie?
Why would they say both died that day?
Because you said
you didn't remember the incident.
So they decided to cover up everything.
Your father's family kept you in the dark.
They're both alive.
Wonderful.
Wonderful, Hiro.
That was just incredible.
And what you did
with the action sequence is…
Wow.
I desperately wanted to join this project,
so I shot that in a hurry.
Thank you for your kind words.
Well, I'm very flattered, Hiro.
And I'll be honest,
knowing how popular you are in Japan,
I was surprised
when you asked to audition.
I prepared some words
to say on my own without an interpreter.
Even though I'm a big fan of your movies,
I couldn't even ask
for an audition because
I was scared of being rejected.
But I've learned one thing.
If I don't fight for something
I really want,
I will be left with
nothing but regret.
This time,
I will not run away from the fight.
That's very touching. Thank you.
You've changed, Hiro.
You've matured.
After what happened,
your father couldn't bear to see you.
We had no other choice but to take you in.
I didn't come here to accuse you.
I let it go.
I'm here to ask you for a favor.
My goal is to find my mother,
and Dad is the one who knows her.
He is the closest person to her,
and he would know where she is.
Ask him, please.
He could help me find her at least.
You're planning to see your mother again?
I just need to see her in person.
I wanna be free and let go of all of it.
I understand.
I know, but still,
I can't help but worry.
Don't worry, I'll be fine.
I can always use Papago.
Although everyone speaks English there,
so I won't need to.
I could still go.
Just as… as moral support,
if you need me to be with you.
I've said to you
that we can't ever have
a real happy ending together, Ho-jin.
So you offering to join me is sweet,
but kind of unnecessary and ridiculous
since we are going to break up.
I don't want us to break up for good,
you know?
So I think that we should…
break up right now,
and we can do it right here.
I'll come back and I'll threaten you
and force you into dating me again.
So then, you'll have to give in,
and I'm sure
we'll be happy together forever.
I don't ever give in to threats.
You better be prepared.
I know I can take it.
Yes, I will.
I wonder if she's okay.
Ho-jin? Do you mind
if I take some of these sauces?
They're better than my mom's.
Sure, go ahead.
And this one too?
Oh, how about this one? It's so good.
-Take them all.
-Do you have a bigger one?
It's there by the sink.
-The sink?
-I'll find it for you.
No, I've got it.
I know where it is,
so you don't have to go searching.
-Found it.
-You did?
-Good.
-It's this container.
-Take it all.
-Hey. There's another thing.
-You can have that too.
-I…
Take it.
You're picking up some weird habits
from Ji-sun, dude.
The birds are flying…
Why'd you put that bag here?
Something they want to imply
I'll take that.
They're books I'll be donating.
The university library wants them.
I have to think about
what to do with the rest.
-So many paintings and antiques.
-Figure it out now while you're here.
Hey, those pieces are expensive.
I can't sort them out in just one trip.
I'll keep visiting.
It's better if I take my time.
This is a great house,
and you're using it for storage?
So what?
Are you planning on selling it?
Are you moving once you get married?
Oh, this one.
May I take this book with me?
-It's yours.
-Really? Thanks!
-Oh!
-What about this?
Could I also take this with me?
Yes, take that too.
It's a first edition Dickens.
-Oh no. You can't take the Dickens.
-Huh?
-Let me have it.
-Give it back.
-You've already given it to me.
-Why are you so greedy? Give it back.
You don't even look after them.
-I will, especially this.
-Let go! Hey!
You're playing with my heart.
Just let me keep this book.
You can't ask to keep
a first edition Dickens.
Do you know how much it's worth?
-I love this book.
-Give it back.
-No!
-Please.
Should I sell this house and move away?
Mr. Kim! It's mine!
Cha Mu-hee said she likes this house.
I greet the breeze
And nod to the trees
I hear the winds reply
So are you spending New Year's Eve
with your A-list girlfriend?
Stop it.
This year, we've already planned
to celebrate it together.
Do you wanna join us?
-Yes, of course.
-Good. Great.
-Will everyone be coming this year?
-Yeah, of course. They're all coming.
-Okay.
-Maybe you can bring your girlfriend.
She's more than welcome.
I can't.
-Why?
-We're not together.
No way, man.
How do you always get dumped?
I'm leaving.
Okay.
Drop in a bit later.
-Don't wallow alone.
-Got it.
It was great because I was great.
I'm the best.
-I wouldn't go that far.
-Everyone!
Today, we gave the studio our final cut.
Romantic Trip!
We were so close to missing our deadline.
We would have been fined.
My hands were shaking
as I typed the captions.
You'll be shaking again.
When the show comes out
and we get the ratings,
you'll have shivers run down your spine.
Whatever the ratings, our show is fun.
Of course you're not worried.
You're off to the UK.
You'll be asleep
when the ratings come out.
-Oh! So good!
-Look at that!
That's why I'm buying tonight.
Drinks for all.
It's been great working together.
I'm going to miss you.
Thank you so much, everyone.
Shall we raise a glass?
-Let's toast!
-To everyone!
-Everyone, cheers!
-Long time no see.
Good. You're here.
-Welcome.
-I heard you finished, and it'll air soon.
-Good work.
-Don't worry about it.
We did great.
-Our show is gonna be a hit.
-Yeah, sure.
Drink up. It's on me.
I still have the card.
-Amazing!
-Okay!
So you show up like this out of nowhere
and offer to pay the bill for everyone?
Wow, I'm really shocked!
You better not take
the credit for our work.
-I'd never.
-We know him. He will.
And for the next season,
he'll jump right in.
This is how he survives in this industry.
Leaves us and comes back when it's good.
-Happy holidays!
-Happy holidays to everyone!
Cheers!
You see the ray of light
Come down here over me
And now you blow a kiss
From the palm of your hand
The rain is falling down
Just gently through my mind
We're dancing on the clouds
Don't know how…
Honey,
let's see the stars together.
Will you look at that.
What a powerful threat.
Welcome to our observatory,
and thank you for visiting tonight.
This location is the first one in Asia
to be certified by Dark Sky International
as a dark-sky preserve,
which protects the beauty of the night sky
from artificial lights
and light pollution.
Here, you can observe celestial wonders
like the Milky Way
and see shooting stars
just with the naked eye.
As the lights go out
and the darkness settles,
your eyes will adjust slowly,
and the stars will begin
to appear one by one.
We hope you share this beautiful,
unforgettable evening
here at our observatory
with someone special.
Have you come here to see the stars?
I need you to do
a good job translating for me.
He could be mad at me
because I got here late.
Please translate with all your heart.
I've missed you a lot.
Ah. He doesn't like German.
How about Japanese?
I've really missed you.
He still doesn't understand?
I really missed you, Ho-jin.
I missed you so much, honey.
Hmm.
Why aren't you speaking?
You must understand.
You're not saying anything.
Are you angry, Ho-jin?
I'm just at a loss for words.
I couldn't find any.
Have you come to see the stars?
I also have a bouquet of clovers.
This is so we'll have good weather.
If you're mad, please go ahead and swear.
Swear if you don't wanna talk to me.
Or you can use
a language that's universal.
I will.
It's a good option.
That will work.
Finally,
our happy ending is here.
Hold on.
Let's change the music
because our ending is perfectly happy.
CAN THIS LOVE BE TRANSLATED?
Bring me all your love
Bring me
All your love